{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wallcovering \u0026 Wallpaper Repair Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40160/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40160,"taskName":"Wallcovering or Wallpaper - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Wallpaper","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wallcovering \u0026 Wallpaper Repair Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":255,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Wallcovering Wallpaper paint repairation","textMessagingName":"Repr Wallcover","rolloverLongDesc":"Usually wallpaper is not repaired but replaced unless the paper is intact \u0026 only peeling up at the edges. Also, for very expensive or antique coverings, there are specialists who can fashion nearly invisible patches.","rolloverShortDesc":"Re-glue, seal seams \u0026 patch.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Wallpaper.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Wallpaper Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Wallcovering","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":80,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Wallpaper Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Wallcovering or Wallpaper - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wallcovering \u0026 Wallpaper Project","urlName":"Wallcovering-or-Wallpaper-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wallpaper Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews \u0026 Cost Info","searchKeywords":"wallpaper, wall paper, wall coverings, wallcovering","emcCategoryOid":-12075,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":470,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40160/":{"taskOID":40160,"originalTaskOID":40160,"setID":470,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1334,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the problems you need repaired.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4629,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Peeling","answerDisplayText":"Peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rip","answerDisplayText":"Rip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2307,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seams","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3029,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Holes","answerDisplayText":"Holes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1335,"questionDisplayText":"Extra Matching Wallcovering","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have any extra matching wallcovering in storage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1334,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the problems you need repaired.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4629,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Peeling","answerDisplayText":"Peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rip","answerDisplayText":"Rip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2307,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seams","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3029,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Holes","answerDisplayText":"Holes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4629,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Peeling","answerDisplayText":"Peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rip","answerDisplayText":"Rip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2307,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seams","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3029,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Holes","answerDisplayText":"Holes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1335,"questionDisplayText":"Extra Matching Wallcovering","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have any extra matching wallcovering in storage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}